Edward U. Condon Papers 1920-1974 Mss.B.C752
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1920-1974; 128 boxes, 64 linear feet
  - O'Brien, John R. and Associates, Inc. (Box 98)
  - O'Brien, Michael (Box 98)
  - O'Bryan, Henry M. (Box 98)
  - Observer (Box 98)
  - Odabasi, Halis, 5 folders (Box 98)
  - Odabasi, H. Combined Configuration and Magnetic Interaction for Bound Levels of Free Atoms (Box 98)
  - Odabasi, H. Mg1 Isoelectronic Sequence, 5 folders (Box 98)
  - Odishaw, Hugh (Box 99)
  - Offenbacher, Elmer L. (Box 99)
  - Offenhartz, Peter O'D (Box 99)
  - Offenhauser, William H., Jr. (Box 99)
  - Office of Scientific Research and Development (Box 99)
  - O'Hare, Frank P. (Box 99)
  - Ohio Oil Company (Box 99)
  - Ohio State University (Box 99)
  - Ohio University (Box 99)
  - Ohliger, Paul (Box 99)
  - Oksuz, Iskender (Box 99)
  - Olcott, Joseph S. (Box 99)
  - Oldenberg, O. James Franck at GC6ttingen (Box 99)
  - Oliphant, M. L. (Box 99)
  - Oliphant, Sir Mark (Box 99)
  - Ontario Minerals Company (Box 99)
  - Oppenheimer, Frank (Box 99)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 13 folders (Box 99)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, Case, 4 folders (Box 99)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert. The Constitution of Matter (Box 99)
  - Optical Society of America, 5 folders (Box 99)
  - Optical Spectra (Box 99)
  - Orden, Alex (Box 99)
  - Order-Disorder Transitions in Alloys (Box 100)
  - Orear, Jay (Box 100)
  - Oregon State University (Box 100)
  - Oster, Ludwig. Some Aspects of Detailed Balancing (Box 100)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 100)
  - P.E.C. Corporation (Box 100)
  - Pacific Coast Unitarian Council (Box 100)
  - Page, Thornton (Box 100)
  - Pake, George E., 4 folders (Box 100)
  - Palace of Arts and Science Foundation, 38 folders (Box 100-101)
  - Palace of Arts and Science Foundation. Letters to Potential Exhibitors, 2 folders (Box 101)
  - Palme, J. R. (Box 101)
  - Palmer, Dewey H. (Box 101)
  - Palmer, E. Laurence (Box 101)
  - Palmer, Edward Paul (Box 101)
  - Palmer, Theodore W. (Box 101)
  - On the Possible Use of Non-Single-Valued Wave Functions in Quantum Mechanics, Pandres, Dave (Box 101)
  - Park, David (Box 101)
  - Parker, Vincent E. (Box 101)
  - Parkins, William E. (Box 101)
  - Parmenter, Richard (Box 101)
  - Paschkis, Victor (Box 101)
  - Paterson (Box 101)
  - Patterson, A. L. (Box 101)
  - Patterson, George W. (Box 101)
  - Patterson, Mrs. Harriet W. (Box 101)
  - Patterson, J. D. (Box 101)
  - Patterson, John C. (Box 101)
  - Patterson, Robert P. (Box 101)
  - Pauling, Ava Helen (Box 101)
  - Pauling, Linus, 6 folders (Box 101)
  - Payne, Fernandus (Box 101)
  - Peace News (Box 101)
  - Pearson, Mrs. Denise Royal (Box 101)
  - Pearson, Drew (Box 101)
  - Peck, Gordon V. (Box 101)
  - Pecker, Jean-Claude (Box 101)
  - Peel, J. J. (Box 101)
  - Pellam, John R. (Box 101)
  - Pendray, G. Edward (Box 101)
  - Pennsylvania Association of College Chemistry Teachers (Box 101)
  - Pennsylvania State College (Box 101)
  - Quantization Rules for Non-Separable Systems, 2 folders; Percival, I. C. (Box 101)
  - Perkes, C. (Box 101)
  - Personnel Security Question (Box 101)
  - Peters, Bernard, 2 folders (Box 101)
  - Peters, John P. vs. Oveta C. Hobby, et. al. (Box 101)
  - Peters, William R. (Box 101)
  - Peterson, Helen (Box 101)
  - Pfeiffer, E. W. (Box 101)
  - Pfeiffer, Eugene (Box 101)
  - Phelps, Arthur V. (Box 101)
  - Phelps, John B. (Box 101)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 13 folders (Box 101-102)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Christian Gauss Award Committee (Box 102)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Ralph Waldo Emerson Award Committee (Box 102)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Science Award Committee, 5 folders (Box 102)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Senator-at-Large, 22 folders (Box 102)
  - Phi Lambda Upsilon (Box 102)
  - Philharmonic Symphony Intermission Science Talks, 2 folders (Box 102)
  - Phillips, J. Marque (Box 102)
  - Phillips, Lindsay F. (Box 102)
  - Phillips, Melba, 3 folders (Box 102)
  - Phillips Academy (Box 102)
  - Philosophical Society of Washington, 8 folders (Box 102-103)
  - Philosophy of Science Association (Box 103)
  - Physical Review (Box 103)
  - Physical Society of Japan (Box 103)
  - Physical Society (London), 3 folders (Box 103)
  - Physical Society of Pittsburgh (Box 103)
  - Physics, 13 folders (Box 103)
  - Physics Bulletin, 3 folders (Box 103)
  - Physics Club of Chicago (Box 103)
  - Physics Today (Box 103)
  - Pief (Box 103)
  - Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - Antidote to Anti-Science, Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - For the Living Generation, 3 folders; Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - Justification for a University, Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - On the Feasibility of Peace, 2 folders; Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - Science, Disarmament and Peace, Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - Treason of the Clerks, 2 folders; Piel, Gerard (Box 103)
  - Pinchot, Cornelia Bryce, 2 folders (Box 104)
  - Pinchot, Gifford Bryce (Box 104)
  - Pinchot, Marianna (Box 104)
  - Pinchot, Sandy (Box 104)
  - Pioneers, Inc. (Box 104)
  - Piore, E. R. (Box 104)
  - Pittsburgh [Pa.] Jaycees (Box 104)
  - Placek, Mrs. Robert (Box 104)
  - Planck, Max. Eight Lectures on Theoretical Physics (Box 104)
  - Planeview [Wichita, Kan.] School Libraries (Box 104)
  - Platt, John (Box 104)
  - Pline, Richard A. (Box 104)
  - Plowshare (Canal Excavating Project) (Box 104)
  - Podolsky, Boris (Box 104)
  - Polarizability of a Fermi-Dirac Electron Gas (Box 104)
  - Pollack, Philip (Box 104)
  - Pollard, Ernest (Box 104)
  - Poncelet, Eugene F. The Mechanism of Flow in Condensed Phases. (Box 104)
  - Porter, Charles O. (Box 104)
  - Postmaster [Aspen, Colo.] (Box 104)
  - Postmaster [Corning, N.Y.} (Box 104)
  - Potter, Alden A. (Box 104)
  - Potter, Russell (Box 104)
  - Poveda, Arcadio (Box 104)
  - Pre-Med Physics Study, 2 folders (Box 104)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 6 folders (Box 104)
  - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America (Box 104)
  - Present, Richard D. (Box 104)
  - President's Committee on the National Medal of Science (Box 104)
  - President's Scientific Research Board, 1947, 5 folders (Box 104)
  - Pressure Broadening, 3 folders (Box 104)
  - Price, Albert (Box 104)
  - Price, Charles C. (Box 104)
  - Price, Waterhouse and Company (Box 104)
  - Princeton Club of New York (Box 104)
  - Princeton University, 5 folders (Box 104)
  - Princeton University. Advisory Council, 4 folders (Box 104)
  - Princeton University. Advisory Council. Report (Box 104)
  - Princeton University. Trustees, 2 folders (Box 105)
  - Princeton University. Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs (Box 105)
  - Princeton University Press (Box 105)
  - X-Ray Induced Electrical Polarization in Glass, Proctor, T. M. (Box 105)
  - Project Blue Book, 4 folders (Box 105)
  - Project Blue Book. Case Studies - Boston, Mass. (Box 105)
  - Project Blue Book. Case Studies - Exeter, N.H., 4 folders (Box 105)
  - Project Blue Book. Case Studies - Harrisonburg, Va., 3 folders (Box 105)
  - Project Blue Book. Case Studies - Walesville, N.Y. (Box 105)
  - Proxmire, William (Box 105)
  - Prudential Insurance Company of America (Box 105)
  - Public Service Company of Colorado (Box 105)
  - Puck, Theodore T. (Box 105)
  - Glass Cracking Caused by High Explosives., Pugh, E. M., R. V. Heine-Geldern, S. Foner, and E. C. Mutschler. (Box 105)
  - Pugh, George (Box 105)
  - Pulkovo [U.S.S.R.] Observatory - Photographs (Box 105)
  - Purcell, Katherine M. (Box 105)
  - Purdue University (Box 105)
  - Quackenboss (Box 105)
  - A Quaker Action Group (Box 105)
  - Quaker Program at the United Nations (Box 105)
  - Quantum Mechanics - Lecture Notes. (Box 105)
    See: Course Materials. Quantum Mechanics - Lecture Notes
  - Quantum Theory of Matter. Editorial Board. (Box 105)
  - Rabi, Isidor I. (Box 105)
  - Rabinow, Jack (Box 105)
  - Sundry Reprints (Box 105)
  - Radiation Theory - Quantum (Box 105)
  - Radiative Transport in Hot Glass, 21 folders (Box 105)
  - Radio Corporation of America, 2 folders (Box 105)
  - Radio Reports, Inc. (Box 105)
  - Raich, John C. (Box 105)
  - Ramge, Harry H. (Box 106)
  - Ramsay, C. A. (Box 106)
  - Ramsey, Norman F. (Box 106)
  - Rand Corporation (Box 106)
  - American College Dictionary, 2 folders; Random House, Inc. (Box 106)
  - Rao, Bijan K. (Box 106)
  - Rasetti, Franco (Box 106)
  - Rasmussen, John (Box 106)
  - Ratchford, J. Thomas (Box 106)
  - Rathjen, Mrs. Henry (Box 106)
  - Read, Thomas (Box 106)
  - Read, Thornton. A Proposal to Neutralize Nuclear Weapons (Box 106)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation. Office of Rubber Reserve (Box 106)
  - Rees, Mina (Box 106)
  - Rees, Thomas (Box 106)
  - Reference Committee on Nuclear Physics & Isotopes (Box 106)
  - Regenorter, Henri van (Box 106)
  - Reich, Franny (Box 106)
  - Reid, J. Gilman (Box 106)
  - Reines, Frederick (Box 106)
  - Reinhold Book Division (Box 106)
  - Reinhold Publishing Corporation (Box 106)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (Box 106)
  - "Reporter Edward Condon," SR, February 1, 1969 (Box 106)
  - Reprints, requests for (with replies), 3 folders (Box 106)
  - Research Corporation, 2 folders (Box 106)
  - Research Institute for Advanced Studies, 3 folders (Box 106)
  - Reston, James B. (Box 106)
  - Retirement Dinner, May 25, 1970 (Box 106)
  - Review of Scientific Instruments. (Box 106)
    See: American Institute of Physics
  - Reviews of Modern Physics (Box 106)
    See: American Physical Society
  - Reynolds, B. D. (Box 106)
  - Reynolds, Vitha B. (Box 106)
  - Rhine, J. B. (Box 106)
  - Rhoades, D. A. (Box 106)
  - Rice, F. O. (Box 106)
  - Richard, John F. (Box 106)
  - Ridenour, Louis N. (Box 106)
  - A Bibliography of Selected Physics Films, Riley, William R. (Box 106)
  - Rinehart, Marion (Box 106)
  - Ritland, Harold (Box 106)
  - Roberts, A. (Box 106)
  - Roberts, Alpheus J. (Box 106)
  - Magnetic Torque on Silicon-Oxygen Tetrahedron Pairs, Roberts, Newton K. and Martin J. McKenley. (Box 106)
  - Roberts, Walter Orr, 2 folders (Box 106)
  - Robertson, H. P. (Box 106)
  - Robertson, Percival (Box 106)
  - Robinson, E. S. (Box 106)
  - Robinson, G. C. (Box 106)
  - Rochester (N.Y.) Association for the United Nations (Box 106)
  - Rochester (N.Y.) Democrat and Chronicle (Box 106)
  - Rockwell, Robert (Box 106)
  - Rocky Mountain Herald (Denver, Colo.) (Box 106)
  - Rodney, William S. (Box 106)
  - Roe, Hamilton L. (Box 106)
  - Rohrlich, Fritz (Box 106)
  - Roitman, George H. (Box 106)
  - Rojansky, Vladimir (Box 106)
  - Rollefson, R. (Box 106)
  - Roller, Duane (Box 106)
  - Romig, Mary F. (Box 106)
  - Rona-Ehrenhaft, Lilly (Box 106)
  - Ronneberg, Conrad E. (Box 106)
  - Rop, Kenneth J. (Box 106)
  - Rorschach, H. E., Jr. (Box 106)
  - Rose, D. J. (Box 106)
  - Roseburg, Ted (Box 106)
  - Rosebury, Amy and Ted (Box 106)
  - Rosenberg, Alburt M. (Box 106)
  - Rosenman, Samuel I. (Box 106)
  - Ross, Robert H., Jr. (Box 106)
  - Rossini, Frederick D. (Box 106)
  - Royal Norwegian Society for the Sciences (Box 107)
  - Royal Society of Arts (Box 107)
  - Royal Swedish Academy (Box 107)
  - Ruark, Arthur E. (Box 107)
  - Rudolph, Marguerita (Box 107)
  - Runge, C. Graphical Methods (Box 107)
  - Russian Science Dictionary - Translation Project (Box 107)
  - Ryanec, E. A. (Box 107)
  - Sabath, Adolph J. (Box 107)
  - Pauli Exclusion Principle From A Self-Consistent Field Theory of Quantum Electrodynamics, Sachs, Mendel. (Box 107)
  - St. Louis (Mo.) Globe-Democrat (Box 107)
  - St. Louis (Mo.) Post-Dispatch (Box 107)
  - Salam, Abdus (Box 107)
  - A World Federation of Institutes of Advanced Study, Salam, Abdus, 1926-1996 (Box 107)
  - Salisbury, Winfield (Box 107)
  - Sampson, Mrs. Jean (Box 107)
  - San Francisco [Calif.] Chronicle (Box 107)
  - Sanders, B. S. (Box 107)
  - Sanderson, Elbert (Box 107)
  - Sandow, Alexander (Box 107)
  - Sands, R. H. (Box 107)
  - SANE, 6 folders (Box 107)
  - Saporoschenko, Mykola (Box 107)
  - Sard, R. D. (Box 107)
  - Eigenvalues of Fermion Density Matrices, Sasaki, Fukashi. (Box 107)
  - Satellite Education TV (Box 107)
  - Saturday Evening Post (Box 107)
  - Saturday Review (Box 107)
  - Saville, Thorndike (Box 107)
  - Sawyer, Charles (Box 107)
  - Scarlott, Charles A. (Box 107)
  - Schaden, Harry E. (Box 107)
  - Schaerf, Henry M. (Box 107)
  - Schaffner, Joseph Halle (Box 107)
  - Schapsmeier, Edward L. (Box 107)
  - Schick, Judi (Box 107)
  - Schiff, L. I. (Box 107)
  - Schimmel, Herbert (Box 107)
  - Schindler, Alfred (Box 107)
  - Schlytter, Leslie Evan (Box 107)
  - Schmidt, F. H. (Box 107)
  - Schmidt, Paul C. (Box 107)
  - Schmitt, Francis O. (Box 107)
  - Schoenfelder, C. W. (Box 107)
  - Schoepfle, G. K. (Box 107)
  - Schoonover, Irl C. (Box 107)
  - Schor, Harold (Box 107)
  - Schufle, J. A. (Box 107)
  - Schuler, Frederic (Box 107)
  - Schulman, James H. (Box 107)
  - N=15 Isoelectronic Sequences, 2 folders; Schultz, Ward (Box 107)
  - Schulz, Paul W. (Box 107)
  - Science, 2 folders (Box 108)
  - Science and Society - College Courses, 9 folders (Box 108)
  - Science Digest (Box 108)
  - Science Research Associates (Box 108)
  - Science Service, 4 folders (Box 108)
  - Scientific American, 5 folders (Box 108)
  - Scientific Manpower Commission (Box 108)
  - Scientific Monthly (Box 108)
  - Scientific Research Society of America (Box 108)
  - Scientist's Committee on Chemical and Biological Warfare (Box 108)
  - Scientists and Engineers. Committee for Johnson (Box 108)
  - Scientists and Engineers. Committee for McCarthy (Box 108)
  - Scientists and Engineers for Social and Political Action, 2 folders (Box 108)
  - Scientists' Committee on Loyalty Problems, 3 folders (Box 108)
  - Scientists for Social and Political Action (Box 108)
  - Scott, Russell B. (Box 108)
  - Scott, William T. The Evolution of the Electromagnetic Field Concept (Box 108)
  - Scull, David H. (Box 108)
  - Seaborg, Glenn T. (Box 108)
  - Sears, Paul B. (Box 108)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Company (Box 108)
  - Second European Regional Meeting in Astronomy (Box 108)
  - Security Investigations, 1948, 9 folders (Box 108)
  - Security Investigations, 1948. Public Reaction to Rep. J. P. Thomas' Attack., 5 folders (Box 108)
  - Security Investigations, 1948 to 1952. Drafts of Statements, Letters, etc. That Were Not Used., 19 folders (Box 108)
  - Security Investigations, 1949, 4 folders (Box 108)
  - Security Investigations, 1949. Public Reaction to J. Edgar Hoover's Remarks., 6 folders (Box 109)
  - Security Investigations, 1950, 3 folders (Box 109)
  - Security Investigations, 1951, 3 folders (Box 109)
  - Security Investigations, 1952, 11 folders (Box 109)
  - Security Investigations, 1953, 12 folders (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations, 1954, 8 folders (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations, 1954. Index of Criticisms Made Relative to Dr. Condon's Activities and Associations - Together With Answers Thereto., 5 folders (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations, 1955 (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations, 1956, 2 folders (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations, 1966, 2 folders (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations, 1969 (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations. Loyalty Discussions, 6 folders (Box 110)
  - Security Investigations. Recipients of Condon testimony reprint (Box 110)
  - Seeger, Raymond J. (Box 110)
  - Seeley, H. (Box 110)
  - Seitz, Frederick, 7 folders (Box 110)
  - Seitz, Frederick and Albert Sherman. On the Symmetric States of Atomic Configurations. (Box 110)
  - Seldin, Jonathan P. (Box 110)
  - Selected Topics in Theoretical Physics. (Box 110)
    See: Course Materials. Selected Topics in Theoretical Physics
  - Seliger, Howard E. (Box 110)
  - Sellers, Robert F. (Box 110)
  - Sellin, Thorsten (Box 110)
  - Semi-Elements, Inc., 2 folders (Box 111)
  - Semmelmeyer, Mrs. John A., Jr. (Box 111)
  - Series, G. W. The Rôle of the Final State in Radiation Processes. (Box 111)
  - Servel, Inc. (Box 111)
  - Seubert, Eugene E. (Box 111)
  - A Systematic Treatment of the Low Configurations in the Spectra of the Transition Groups., Shadmi, Yehuda. (Box 111)
  - Shaffer, Jerome (Box 111)
  - Shaffer, Ralph E. (Box 111)
  - Glass Panel Radiant Heating, Shand, E. B. (Box 111)
  - Shane, Charles Donald (Box 111)
  - Shank, Paul (Box 111)
  - Shankland, R. S. (Box 111)
  - Shapiro, Ascher H. (Box 111)
  - Shapiro, Maurice M. (Box 111)
  - Shapiro, Nathan (Box 111)
  - Shapley, Alan (Box 111)
  - Shapley, Harlow (Box 111)
  - Shaver, W. W. (Box 111)
  - Shaw, Rodney (Box 111)
  - Shaw, Stuart (Box 111)
  - Spin-One Particle in an External Electromagnetic Field, Shay, D. (Box 111)
  - Shepley, Ethan A. H. (Box 111)
  - Sheraton Park Hotel (Box 111)
  - Special Theory of Relativity, 4 folders; Sherman, N. (Box 111)
  - Shockley, William (Box 111)
  - Theory of Atomic Spectra on the Five Electron Isoelectric Series Bl-Pxl, 10 folders; Shonk, Carl Richter (Box 111)
  - Shore Conference on Atomic Information (Box 111)
  - Shortley, George H., 6 folders (Box 111)
  - Shoupp, W. E. (Box 111)
  - Siddeek, Maria (Box 111)
  - Siegel, Sidney (Box 111)
  - Sigma Phi Sigma (Box 111)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 111)
  - Silberstein, Richard (Box 111)
  - Silon, Herbert (Box 111)
  - Silverman, Alexander (Box 111)
  - Silverman, Richard (Box 111)
  - Silverman, Shirleigh (Box 111)
  - Simon, Sir Francis E. (Box 111)
  - Simon, Ivan (Box 111)
  - Simon and Schuster, Inc. (Box 111)
  - Simonson, Ernst (Box 111)
  - Simpson, O. C. (Box 111)
  - Sinai Temple Forum (Box 112)
  - Sinanoglu, Oktay, 6 folders (Box 112)
  - Sinanoglu, Mrs. Paula (Box 112)
  - Singer, Fred (Box 112)
  - Singer, J. David (Box 112)
  - Singer, S. F. (Box 112)
  - Sitterly, Charlotte M. (Box 112)
  - Skolnikoff, E. B. (Box 112)
  - Slater, John C. (Box 112)
  - Slaughter, Lawrence H. (Box 112)
  - Slepian, Joseph, 3 folders (Box 112)
  - Slichter, Charles P. (Box 112)
  - Sloan, Louise (Box 112)
  - Smiley, Joseph R. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Alice Kimball (Box 112)
  - Smith, Cecil R., Jr. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Cyril Stanley (Box 112)
  - Smith, Mrs. Cyril (Box 112)
  - Smith, David A. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Edwin S. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Ethel Marie (Box 112)
  - Smith, Gail P. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Huston (Box 112)
  - Smith, Jane (Box 112)
  - Smith, Joe (Box 112)
  - Asymptotic Wave Functions Near Thresholds in the Presence of Long-Range Potentials, Smith, Kenneth. (Box 112)
  - Smith, M. W. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Marian W. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Paul A. (Box 112)
  - Matrix Representation of Relations Between Systems of Units, 2 folders; Smith, Paul A. (Box 112)
  - Smith, Stephen J. (Box 112)
  - Stephen J. Smith vs. Katharine Gebbie and Richard Thomas, 3 folders (Box 112)
  - Smithsonian Institution (Box 112)
  - Smyth, H. D. (Box 112)
  - Smyth, Henry D. (Box 112)
  - Snow, Joel Alan, 2 folders (Box 112)
  - Snyder, Ralph (Box 112)
  - Relativistic Energies in Isoelectric Sequences, 4 folders; Snyder, Ralph Brockett (Box 112)
  - Sobell, Morton (Box 112)
  - Social Science Institute (Box 112)
  - Societa Italiana di Fisica (Box 112)
  - Société Française de Physique (Box 112)
  - Society for Advancement of Management, Inc. (Box 112)
  - Society for Applied Spectroscopy (Box 112)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science, 53 folders (Box 112-113)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science. Newsletter (Box 113)
  - Society of Applied Spectroscopy (Box 113)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers, Inc. (Box 113)
  - Society of Engineering Science (Box 113)
  - Society of Friends (Quakers) (Box 114)
    See: Friends
  - Society of Glass Technology (Box 114)
  - Society of Systematic Zoology (Box 114)
  - Society of the Sigma Xi (Box 114)
  - Solandt, Donald Y. (Box 114)
  - de Solla Price, Derek J. (Box 114)
  - Somerville, Mrs. Ernest T. (Box 114)
  - Sood, P. C. (Box 114)
  - Sopka, John J. (Box 114)
  - Sopka, Katherine J. (Box 114)
  - Sosman, Robert B. (Box 114)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund, Inc. (Box 114)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare (Box 114)
  - Sowden, John C. (Box 114)
  - Spanel, Abram N., 2 folders (Box 114)
  - Spanel, Mrs. Abram N. (Box 114)
  - Spectrolab (Box 114)
  - Spectroscopy Research Institute, 3 folders (Box 114)
  - Spence, Kenneth (Box 114)
  - Spin, 2 folders (Box 114)
  - Spitzer, R. R. (Box 114)
  - Sprague Electric Company (Box 114)
  - Springer-Verlag (Box 114)
  - Springfield [High Point, N.C.] Friends Meeting (Box 114)
  - Sproul, Robert G. (Box 114)
  - Stabler, Harold B. (Box 114)
  - Statement to Fellow Scientists and Physicians, Stamler, Jeremiah (Box 114)
  - Legal Aid Fund, 10 folders; Stamler, Jeremiah, M.D. (Box 114)
  - Stanford University (Box 114)
  - Starr, Chauncey (Box 114)
  - Benefit-Cost Relationships in Socio-Technical Systems, Starr, Chauncey (Box 114)
  - Utilization of Scientific and Technical Resources in Overcoming Problems, Starr, Chauncey (Box 114)
  - Statistical Mechanics, 6 folders (Box 114)
  - Statistical Theory of Distribution of Wealth, 3 folders (Box 114)
  - Statler Hotel (Box 115)
  - Stearns, Robert L. (Box 115)
  - Steele, Howard (Box 115)
  - Steelman, John Roy (Box 115)
  - Steiner, Oscar (Box 115)
  - Stepanek, Antoinette. (Box 115)
    See: Stepanek, Joseph E.
  - Stepanek, Joseph E., 7 folders (Box 115)
  - Stepanek, Toni (Box 115)
  - Stephens, W. E. (Box 115)
  - Stern, Philip M. (Box 115)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Box 115)
  - Stevenson, Earl P. (Box 115)
  - Stewart, G. W. (Box 115)
  - Stewart, John W. (Box 115)
  - Still, Joseph W. (Box 115)
  - Stitt, Robert (Box 115)
  - Stone, Esther (Box 115)
  - Stone, I. F. (Box 115)
  - Stoner, John O., Jr. (Box 115)
  - Stookey, S. Donald (Box 115)
  - Photosensitive Glass, Stookey, S. Donald (Box 115)
  - Spectrometric Determination of Electron Temperatures > 100 EV*+, Stratton, T. F. (Box 115)
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 3 folders (Box 115)
  - Strelkov, Peter G. (Box 115)
  - Strickland, Donald A. (Box 115)
  - Stroke, Henry (Box 115)
  - Strong, John (Box 115)
  - Structure of Molecules, 1934, 2 folders (Box 115)
  - Stuart, Evelyn Marie (Box 115)
  - Students for Democratic Action. Cornell Chapter. (Box 115)
  - Transition Probabilities From Quantized States to Non-Quantized States in Diatomic Molecules., Stueckelberg, E. C. G., (Ernst Carl Gerlach), 1905-1984 (Box 115)
  - Sturrock, Peter A. (Box 115)
  - Equation of State for Hadronic Matter Produced, Suhonen,. E. (Box 115)
  - Sulkow, Martin (Box 115)
  - Sullivan, Patrick M. (Box 115)
  - Sullivan, Thomas P. (Box 115)
  - Sullivan, Walter (Box 115)
  - Sumner, Ray S. (Box 115)
  - Sundaram, S. (Box 115)
  - Sutton, Paul M. (Box 115)
  - Sutton, Richard M. (Box 115)
  - Swarthmore College (Box 115)
  - Subatomic Particles, Swartz, Clifford E. (Box 115)
  - Swings, J. P. (Box 115)
  - Switzer, Mary E. (Box 115)
  - Sydney Morning Herald Limited (Box 115)
  - Syed, Bashir A. (Box 115)
  - Symposium on Quantum Mechanical Tunneling. March 1969 (Box 115)
  - Symposium on the Reactivity of Solids (Box 115)
  - Szilard, Leo (Box 115)
  - Table of Relative Line Strengths for Electric Quadrupole Radiation (Box 116)
  - Tabor, Harry (Box 116)
  - Tata Institute of Fundamental Research, 4 folders (Box 116)
  - Tate, John T. (Box 116)
  - Tawney, Jerry (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Glen H. (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Harold (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Harold. Riots, Wars and American Education (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Lauriston S. (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Leland H. (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Mary C. (Box 116)
  - Taylor, Raymond L. (Box 116)
  - Thermodynamic Functions of Crystals from the Moments of the Frequency Distribution, Taylor, William J. (Box 116)
  - Teachers Defense Committee (Box 116)
  - Teachers Union of Philadelphia (Box 116)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York (Box 116)
  - Telkes, Maria (Box 116)
  - Teller, Edward (Box 116)
  - Teller Institute, 3 folders (Box 116)
  - Temple University (Box 116)
  - Tensmeyer, L. G. (Box 116)
  - Terhune, Robert W. (Box 116)
  - Nonlinear Optics, 7 folders; Terhune, Robert W. and P.D. Maker (Box 116)